["Only One Man" playing]
♪ The only one man ♪
♪ Tu m'en as fait vivre des délices ♪
♪ Je t'en ai fait vivre des supplices ♪
Thanks.
For what?
Walking me home, the beach,
for wagging with me all day.
It was nice.
What about last night? And this morning?
That was a bit of fun.
What, just a bit?
My mum's inside.
Yeah.
See you at school tomorrow!
And do your homework, yeah?
No slacking off.
[Malakai chuckles]
["On The Move" playing]
♪ Been on the move
On a move, on the move ♪
♪ Off the D'usse
Fuck you say ♪
♪ I been on that grind my whole life ♪
♪ So who are you
Who are you, who are you, who are you ♪
♪ No you cannot kill my vibe ♪
♪ So get gone or take this ride ♪
[Quinni] I'm so excited
for Slay Ball this weekend.
[sighs] The pink washing that goes on
around Mardi Gras is so gross.
Yeah, but it's queer X-mas.
- And a chance to get naked!
- No!
Where have you been all my life?
I took a self-care day.
Good for you.
Thanks. I went to the beach,
had some fish and chips, had some sex.
- What?
- Your girl dropped the V plates!
You couldn't tell, could you?
I don't feel that different.
Do I look different? Am I glowing?
No. But you do have
a cornflake on your shirt.
[Darren] Who with?
No, wait, let me guess.
Malakai.
[chuckles] Twenty-four hours ago you swore
you would never touch a dick again.
And here you are.
Amerie has entered the chat.
- Yes. Don't get too excited.
- I'm so proud of you.
Is his dick big?
- [Darren] How many times did you cum?
- [Amerie] I do not cum and tell.
[Darren] Ew. The school
is back on its gay shit.
Mmm.
It's totally not a serious thing though.
I think we're both going to keep it chill.
[rock song playing]
[laughing]
Yeah, that seems totally chill.
[Darren clears throat]
You and Malakai, huh?
You kept that secret.
Dark horse. Am I allowed to say that?
It's not racist, is it?
I don't think so.
Cool. He's a good dude. Oh, and thanks
for the intel on Harper. It helped.
A lot.
That's cool. You and Harper. I'm so glad.
Thanks, Am. It probably never
would have happened without you.
See you around.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Flowers. That's very het.
What did you say?
I made some kind of whale call.
A click, a whistle or a pulsed call?
A sound. It wasn't a no,
but it really, really wasn't a yes.
I don't know what to do, guys.
I only hooked up with him because
Harper came to mine and we had it out
and I was sad and clearly Harper did too
'cause she and Dusty are going steady now.
[Darren] Forget those two.
You don't have to be his girlfriend, but
at least invite him to my pre's tomorrow.
- Yes!
- Then make up your mind.
Do we need to get some...
Oh, yes. Caps all the way.
[whispers] MDMA.
[Darren clears throat]
Oh, um, Cash has us sorted.
He actually might come too.
What? I'm sorry.
The eshay is coming with us to Mardi Gras.
Uh, we want drugs, don't we?
Touchy.
Okay, he's doing us a solid.
You like Cash!
Ew, no, I don't.
Oh, snap.
When did this happen?
A while ago. I don't know what's going on,
so I'm inviting him to find out.
- [exhales]
- Ooh!
Cash, my eshay baby.
Yeah. Okay. All right, cute.
[Amerie] Sucking my dick
all night long. Oh, Cash, yeah.
[Sasha and Quinni whispering, laughing]
Oh, I need to breathe.
[chuckles] Okay. That's very fair.
It's getting quite hot in here.
Um...
I know we said we'd meet up at Slay Ball,
but Darren's having pre's at theirs.
Do you want to come?
Yeah, of course.
Okay, cool.
- Cool.
Who's going?
Uh, me, Darren, Amerie,
and Cash now too, apparently.
- Cool.
- I can't wait to show you my outfit.
Yeah?
What about what's underneath your outfit?
Are we about to have sex
in the nurse's office?
Why? Do you want to?
Um...
We don't have to if you don't want to.
We can take our time
if that's what you want.
I think so.
- Yeah, of course.
- [door opens]
What a coincidence. You two
in the sick bay again, at the same time.
- [fake coughs]
- [laughing]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [boy 1 laughing]
My man. Acting all gentle and shit.
Get 'em!
- I haven't got her yet, bro.
- [Ant] What were the flowers for?
[chuckles] He's a simp, not a pimp.
[boy 2] Simp!
Congratulations, Spider.
You made A-grade. You happy?
If you put as much effort in training
as you did trying to cop a root,
you'd have made the team.
- [laughter]
- [boy 3] So true.
At least there you had a chance, bro.
Ah. See, when I play I always score,
on and off the court.
- [boy 4] Big dog.
- [Spider] Oh, shit, big man.
So you did hook up with Amerie?
[boy 5] Oh, bro, he did.
- [Spider] Bullshit.
- [boy 5] He did it.
When?
- Don't be jealous 'cause a girl picked me.
- [laughter]
- I don't give a shit about Amerie.
- [boy 6 laughs] As if.
Go put your clown makeup on, mate.
[scoffs]
- Shit.
- So, uh, did you hit it from the back?
- Like that. Or two legs?
- Yeah? Side to side?
- Oh, Malakai.
- You Cirque du Soleil that pussy? [Moans]
[Dusty] Did you slap one on?
- [Ant] What? No, dummy?
- [boy 7] What?
Guy isn't looking for a woman,
he's looking to be father of the year.
Did you pull out?
Tell me you pulled out.
No, he's a nice guy.
Probably just jizzed on himself.
Bro, I had to. She was on top.
[boys whistles and cheers]
[imitates moan]
- Can you get me a towel, please?
- Shut up!
- [laughter]
- Oi! Gymnasium now!
Wakey, wakey, ladies! Move it.
Come on. You too, Curly Sue.
That's the way, Mr. District No-Show.
Good of you to join us.
All right! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
[school bell ringing]
Help me put these out before Jojo comes.
Ha! I don't do stage management.
I am the talent.
Amerie, it's already on the map.
[scoffs] Why? No one cares about the map.
Who came up with that
irrelevant shit anyway?
You did.
At least the hookups on here are legit
and not ones from your dreams.
Yeah, but she did kiss Dusty.
[Darren] In her dreams first.
[Quinni] No, but she manifested it.
[Darren] Yeah, in her dreams.
[indistinct chatter]
Missed you.
- How old fashioned of you.
- [chuckles]
Really? So immature.
[chuckles]
What's happening?
We're having Mardi Gras pre's at Darren's.
Want to come?
All right, peeps. Let's pipe down.
Oh, shit. Five-O.
Shelve your pingers, Cash.
Shelve your kiddie porn, rock spider.
[Woodsy] Okay, thank you.
[Jojo] We have two very special guests
speaking with you all today.
I'm told Mr. Peterson is a regular visitor
at the school
and will run you all
through some workshops. Whoo!
Thank you. Uh, hi, everyone,
I'm Kurt Peterson.
And I'm Constable Paul Perry.
But please, guys,
just call me PP. [Chuckling]
- PP?
- [Kurt] So I'm a former police officer.
[fake coughs] ACAB.
And believe it or not, many moons ago,
I was a student here at Hartley High.
So after I graduated,
I decided to join the police force
where I served for over ten years
until injury forced me out.
A question. I like it. Go ahead.
Did you injure yourself from over-policing
a marginalized community?
[laughter]
No, I tripped on a fence.
Right, so, um, we're going
to split the class in two.
The girls are going to come with me and
the boys will stay with Constable Perry.
Darren, you can choose
whichever group you like.
Thank you, Miss. I can tell this is going
to be very problematic.
[indistinct chatter]
[Paul] Lads, you're with me.
Let's get into it.
This program is a young woman's guide
to survival. We call it...
Rack Off.
Sexual assault is a sad reality
for far too many young women.
[Darren] You would know.
And Rack Off is designed to equip you
with the tools and the knowledge
to assist in preventing it.
- [boys] PP! PP! PP! Yeah!
- Ready, set, go! Yes, boys!
The key to unlocking a strong mind
and a strong body is health and fitness.
- True.
- Dude, true.
And it's all in the palm
of your hands, gentlemen.
[grunts] Your phones.
- [laughs]
- Right?
[Kurt] So now you know
the psychology of an offender,
their selection process...
It's time to learn how to get them to...
Rack up?
Rack off.
[sighs]
Uh, so now I'm going to demonstrate
some simple self-defence moves
that you can practise on each other.
So who wants to be a volunteer?
[Sasha giggling]
Come on, guys.
How about you at the back?
[Paul] You at the front.
Show us how many you can do.
- A bit of encouragement!
- [boys cheering]
The rest of you,
I want to hear you count him.
That's called external motivation.
One!
- Two! Three!
- Seven. Fourteen.
- Four!
That's pretty fast. All right,
he'll get tired. Questions, questions.
Can you lift heavy after a wank?
[Paul] Yeah, go heavy.
Always the best after.
- Yeah!
- Sick!
Okay, all right. Yes. Nobody likes
a show-off. Get up. Good job.
Yeah, boy!
I could have done more.
[Paul] Yeah, nice form.
Have you ever shot anyone?
Uh, no.
No, they haven't given me a gun yet.
[Ant] Oh.
But I will. Don't worry.
Yeah, only a matter of time.
[Kurt] A man has a strong grip on you.
Hey, you can't pull down or back,
but the weakest part
of the grip is the thumb.
[voice fades out] You need to cross-grip.
[speaking indistinctly]
[screams]
[girl] What just happened?
Did you just burn me?
Got you to rack off, didn't it?
[chuckling] Uh, okay. I think that's
a really great point to finish up.
Thank you so much.
[Jojo] Wait. Harper!
- He did that. That is...
- Stop.
- It's so outdated.
- [Jojo] All right. Okay.
Um... Tell me something
you all learnt in here today.
Ten thousand steps.
It's all it takes me to become a tank.
[chuckles]
You didn't get the
sexual assault thing we did?
That's bullshit.
We don't need it, all right?
We are all feminists here, yeah?
We know how to ask for consent.
We use protection.
I mean, Malakai the Pullout King,
he just comes on himself.
- Hey.
- How's that for a equality, Amerie?
[Harper] Go climb a waterspout, Spider.
It'll be the closest you come
to getting your dick wet.
Okay, that's enough. Thanks. Thank you.
[school bell ringing]
[Jojo] Thanks, everyone,
enjoy your lunch break.
[indistinct chatter]
Yes.
- Hey, Amerie, I'm really sorry.
- Oi.
- Don't do that.
- What?
I don't need you
to fight my battles for me.
[Spider] Why don't you guys fight again?
That was hot.
[rock music playing on speakers]
Didn't know you would be here.
- Got enough?
- Yeah.
Want one?
If you're offering.
He's probably roofied them.
[Spider] You wish.
I don't trust you. Or that haircut.
Yeah.
You three should play
hide-and-go-fuck-yourselves.
[Spider] Whew.
[burps and exhales]
[upbeat music playing]
[students cheer]
Don't give me a hickey.
- I mean it. I don't feel like it.
- Okay, okay.
Hey, um, you don't
talk to any of
the other guys about us, have you?
What do you mean?
Like about us having sex?
No, of course not.
I'm not like that.
I haven't, all right. I promise.
[sighs]
What?
No.
What? Tell me.
I'm just cut, okay. I don't want you
to think of me like that.
I was just making sure.
Yeah.
Hey.
I don't.
Prove it.
[Cash and Darren laughing]
What have you got now?
Uh, drama. You?
D and T. You want to ditch?
I've wagged every other class.
I might as well keep it consistent.
It always smells like bud around here.
It's probably one of the art teachers.
What's taking so long?
Shit, shit, shit. [Panting]
The bag's gone.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Fuck!
Is that okay? Are the adlays gonna...
What? Finger-bang my face? I hope not.
No, it should be all right.
Let's piss off out of here.
Come on, Susie.
Humping a bike is not hygienic or funny.
Happy Mardi Gras, Miss.
Oh. Thank you.
No, don't eat that. Don't eat that!
Hey.
You better back off.
I learned some defence shit today.
You still wild?
I'm not an animal.
No, not that wild. Black full a wild.
- Just means you're cross with me.
- You think?
Look, it was just the boys.
They made me talk about it.
You know how they go on...
I do, but I didn't think
that you were like that.
This is where you apologize, Malakai.
- Look, I'm sorry. I just...
- No.
If this is how you're going to act,
then that is the answer to the question
you asked me this morning.
Own your shit, dude.
One more order, driver.
Is that enough?
We want two each. [Clears throat]
Oi. Um, it's a bit red-hot right now.
Gundjies everywhere.
Illchay if I get this to you later?
I have no idea what you just said, but it
sounds like now's not a good time. Um...
That's okay.
Just bring it to mine tomorrow?
Yeah, I'll let you know.
[young boy] Oi! Cumgullet!
Is that child talking to you?
Chook is waiting for ya.
What a fucking flamer.
[scoffs]
[pop song playing faintly on speakers]
[Jayden coughs and sniffs]
What's happening, lad?
Fuck all, bro.
[spits]
Where's my kombucha?
I forgot.
[chuckles] Lad, hey?
Go and get it, you little rat.
[sniffles]
How did you go with that
shit from the earch?
[hesitates] Oh, yeah. It was hectic, bro.
Yeah, fully. It was...
[mock stammer]
The fuck are you saying, bro?
You sound like a meth head. What happened?
I haven't been able to sell it, bro.
What do you mean?
A few Unaipons' worth there, mate.
Someone racked it.
Did you get robbed?
No. I had it at Nan's and I moved it
because demons was patrolling,
like you said,
and I put it on the roof at Hartley,
but someone staunched it.
I'll get a back for you, brother. Fully.
Few here now for you.
I want the rest.
The fuck is this?
Peach.
I said lemon!
My fucking TeeNers!
What did you say?
Oi! They're out of lemon, bro.
Not his fault.
You staunching me, bro?
Whose fault is that then, huh?
First you lose my bag
and then you talk shit.
I'll curb stomp you right here.
Don't think that I won't.
Go and get my fucking money.
Take your fucking food with you!
Get in the car.
Get in the car!
["R.I.P" playing]
♪ I'ma do this for you ♪
♪ I been maskin' the pain ♪
♪ Had my heart led astray ♪
♪ Everybody and their dog's on my case ♪
♪ All I really need is space
'Cause I'm lost in my ways ♪
♪ Yeah, I made a mistake ♪
♪ Had it thinking you'd be here forever ♪
♪ You were here, now you're gone ♪
♪ So all I do is mourn, and the pain
It ain't getting' any better ♪
♪ So I be at it, tryna keep my head up ♪
♪ Praying to God for serenity ♪
♪ On my knees, wonder when
The devil gonna let up ♪
♪ Try to cope, but all I think
Of are memories ♪
♪ I'll never say goodbye ♪
- [Darren] Mmm.
- [cell phone chimes]
"It's heaps eetsway.
I'll let you know, bro."
I swear I need subtitles
for him sometimes.
[Amerie] Malakai needs to learn
how to keep his mouth shut.
[Darren] You did
tell us about the hook up.
I kept it PG. Whose side are you on?
Yours, babes.
[Amerie] One-on-one, Malakai is so lovely.
But when guys get into
that group pack mentality,
they just turn so feral.
I'm sorry, boo.
Straight men are the worst.
Mmm.
Lesbians aren't that easy
to deal with either.
- Everybody sucks.
- Mmm.
- Except us.
You know how I feel
about people that aren't us.
- [knock on door]
- Mmm.
I'll check.
[Quinni] I knew Sasha wouldn't show.
[chuckles] I'm so fucking drunk.
[Darren sighs]
Dealing drugs in speed dealers
is a bit cliche, don't you think?
Here.
What happened?
Nothing.
Wait, is that Malakai?
[Amerie] Who is it?
Oh. Just those nice boys we weren't
totally just talking shit about.
You all right, bro?
- Yeah, chilling, bro. All good.
- Hmm.
Hi, just...
Yeah.
Did that little crotch goblin
do that to you?
[chuckles nervously]
No, um, it's just Chook.
I thought you were friends.
We are.
- Your friends are...
- Gronks.
But I grew up with them.
At least you didn't get
finger-fucked in the face.
[chuckles] No. I got fisted.
Aw.
You'll come to the Slay Ball with us?
- [Malakai] Yeah. It'll be cool.
- Cool. It'll be good.
Bold of you to come.
- [pop song playing on speakers]
- [clicks tongue] Ah.
Can we have a yarn
somewhere in private maybe?
I'm gonna go.
- Mmm. No, stay.
- Mm-hmm.
Um...
Did you get any of my messages?
No, I haven't, because you're on mute.
- Right.
- I need to wee.
No, you don't. Sit down.
Mmm. But this is excruciatingly awkward.
- No, it isn't.
- No, it is kind of.
Oh, I'm enjoying watching you squirm.
- Anyway, how'd you get Darren's address?
- I sent him a pin drop.
[whispers] Judas.
[clicks tongue] Anyway, Malakai wants
to talk to you and he wants to say...
I'm really sorry, Amerie.
I messed up. Our business is our business
and no one else's.
I am...
I realize that in my actions,
I was contributing to a culture
- that I don't want any part of.
- [mouthing]
I didn't take into account
how that might make you feel.
I'm sorry.
I promise I'll do better next time.
Well, at least try to.
[pop song continues]
We're gonna need to get you
out of whatever the hell this is.
- [Darren] Mmm.
- What?
Do you want something gay to wear?
Uh... Yes, please.
[squeals] Dress up!
["Black Love" playing]
- ♪ Winter skies ♪
- ♪ Skies ♪
♪ Don't you come my way ♪
Chuck this on.
That's it!
- Okay. Ready? Go like this.
- Yeah?
- ♪ Passion ♪
- ♪ Gotta be worth the pain ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the type
That's flyin' the sky in miles ♪
♪ I'm bout to fly, baby, if it ain't ♪
♪ See, all I'm sayin' is ♪
♪ I just wanna love you ♪
♪ You gotta love me too ♪
♪ Give me reasons to stay, babe ♪
♪ I'm never goin' away 'cause ♪
♪ I just wanna love you ♪
♪ Love you ♪
- ♪ Come in here ♪
- ♪ Come inside ♪
♪ Baby, it's a war outside ♪
♪ This genuine love I give can provide ♪
♪ You a place you can rest and hide ♪
♪ It's real, baby, really all I ask ♪
♪ If you can't provide what I give ♪
♪ Then you'll let this good thing
Just pass you by ♪
Come on. Get a selfie with me!
- Slay Ball!
♪ You gotta love me too ♪
♪ Give me reasons to stay, babe... ♪
This jinger's not going
to give me pink eye, is it?
What's wrong?
[groans] Shoes, I can't find them!
- What's wrong with those?
- They suck!
[Harper groans]
[sighs] I'm just not going to go.
Because your shoes? No.
- Actually, they are pretty terrible.
- [chuckles] Shut up.
Trust me, no one's going
to be looking at your feet.
You're so beautiful.
♪ I just wanna love you ♪
♪ Love you ♪
[sighs]
I know where they are.
[inhales and exhales]
["Work It" playing]
♪ Work, work it ♪
Hey!
♪ Work, work... ♪
I'm so sorry.
Sorry.
[indistinct chatter]
Nice shoes.
Oh, thanks. They're the only thing
of yours I didn't burn.
Oh, look at you.
Acting like you never seen
a Black full a before, hey?
[Malakai chuckles]
Go on, then. Take a picture.
I'm a lovely ting, aren't I?
Don't project your shit
'cause you feel inadequate.
[scoffs] "Inadequate"? Nice.
Big word for a little bloke.
Sorry, sorry.
- LGBTQI-ACAB.
- [sniffles]
Oh, my God. Missy was such a bro-down.
The boys water boarded Spider
with Mountain Dew. So gross.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
You sure?
'Cause you're stimming right now.
Is it getting a little bit too
sensory overload?
No, it's good. I'm fine, Sasha.
Let's just go inside, yeah?
Okay.
♪ I am that ♪
♪ Running it up, drinking the cup
Yes, yes ♪
♪ Drinking the cup, cup, cup, cup ♪
♪ Running it up
Drinking the cup, yes, yes ♪
♪ Drinking the cup, cup, cup, cup, what ♪
[singing indistinctly]
♪ Yes, I'mma go and get that bitch ♪
♪ And go take that bitch
And go boo her hat ♪
♪ Brrr, brrr, brr, brr, brr, brrr, brr ♪
♪ I am that, that
That, that, that, yes ♪
♪ I am that, that, that ♪
♪ I am that, that, that, that, that ♪
♪ I am that, that, that. Yes! ♪
♪ One, one, one, one, one, one, one ♪
♪ Two, two, two, two two, two ♪
♪ Three, three, three, three, three
Now hold that pose for me ♪
[cheers and applause]
[MC] Judges, what is it giving?
[rap song playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Sasha and Missy talking indistinctly]
Sasha?
[laughter]
[laughing stops]
[Sasha] Quinni?
What are you doing?
Oh.
[Missy sniffing]
You want a bump?
Oh, no, she doesn't.
What is it?
[Missy] Ket. It's real nice too.
No, it's sketchy. You don't want any.
[Sasha sniffs]
You're doing it.
And don't fall into another k-hole,
you a-hole.
Shut up. No, it might mess
with your medication.
- Oh.
- You know what I'm feeling? I'm feeling
that we need to go dance.
- You wanna dance? Let's go dance.
- Yes. Yes! Let's go dance.
I'll wait here.
Oh, you sure? We can wait with you.
No, it's fine. Have fun.
Tactical spew? Yeah, tac vom.
- Yeah, it's fine. We got you.
- Okay.
- We'll come back.
- Later.
Okay.
["Just Like This" playing]
♪ Just like this ♪
[people cheering]
[singing] ♪ Am I the only one that's fly
Who do it just like this? ♪
♪ Put my face up, put my tongue up
Baby, just like this ♪
♪ And I would never back down
If you came from my city ♪
♪ Make you feel a little pressure
That's my fist ♪
♪ Am I the only one that's fly
Who do it just like this? ♪
♪ Put my face up, put my tongue up
Baby, just like this ♪
♪ And I would never back down
If you came from my city... ♪
Oi. Where you been, sis?
We haven't had the chance
for proper yarns.
I know. We should link up more often, eh.
Oi.
This necklace is proper deadly, ey.
Here, have it.
[people cheering]
Oi. It's nice to have
another brother around, yeah?
Yeah.
[laughing] This is too dardy.
Your caps kicked in, hasn't it?
I don't know.
I haven't taken drugs before.
[song continues]
[distorted music]
I feel fucking deadly, ey.
[both screaming]
[sighs]
You look amazing.
Thanks.
It was really cool
how you handled that guy yesterday.
I wish I could be more like that.
Like what?
Like a boss. Say and do whatever I want.
Why don't you?
They might stop liking me.
[sighs] We're all gonna die anyway.
So do whatever the fuck you want.
[host] Ladies and gentle-thems,
welcome to the Slay Ball!
[cheers and applause]
If you're a baddie with a body
beyond the binary,
then make your way to the stage
and show us what we want to see.
Next category: Virgin Vogue.
Bring it in an all-white look.
DJ, pump the beat.
[all cheering]
["Tear The House Up" playing]
♪ I'mma tear the house up
And get down on this beat ♪
♪ Down on this beat, down on this beat ♪
♪ I'mma tear the house up
And get down on this beat ♪
♪ Tear the house
♪ I'mma tear the house up
And get down on this beat ♪
♪ Down on this beat, down on this beat ♪
♪ Yo, let's go way, way back
To the basics ♪
♪ Damn motherfuckers
Really just can't take it ♪
♪ Sippin all around
They wanna bite and taste it ♪
♪ I'm that cat, yeah
I'm the black cat, yeah ♪
♪ I'm that bitch that does it like that ♪
♪ You don't got to say it
'Cause the cat got ya tongue ♪
♪ I ain't gotta say it
Bitch, I get it done ♪
♪ Tell me what you did
What you done, done ♪
♪ What, you ain't know it?
Muthafucker, I'm the one ♪
♪ None these bitches
In the back want some... ♪
One. Two. Three. Hold that pose for me.
Judges, scores. Tens, tens.
One chop, baby.
Where is the white?
[both arguing]
We're sorry, but you should've brought it
in a white look.
- We'll see you at the next ball, though.
- [audience booing]
- Bullshit!
- That's bullshit!
It's ballroom, you'll get over it.
["Double Dip" playing]
[girls squealing]
You were absolute fire. Screw that judge.
What? I just got cut from my first walk.
This is the best night of my life.
[Jacob] Darren.
Oh, Jacob. Um... Hi.
You were fucking amazing
out there.
- How are you?
- Thanks.
[inaudible conversation]
♪ Hope nobody saw ♪
♪ Doo doo dat dat dat
Hope nobody saw ♪
♪ Doo doo dat dat dat ♪
♪ Lick, lick, lick, lick ♪
♪ Tastes good, so I double dip ♪
♪ So I double, so I double
So I double, so I double ♪
So I double, so I double... ♪
Chook is a psycho, bro.
- ["What You Like" playing]
- [exhales sharply]
I thought I did pretty good.
Oh, yeah! Fucken oath.
You was a proper gee up.
Right. Yeah, I slayed. [Chuckles]
Then I look around
and [sputters] you were gone.
Yeah, I wanted to talk to you
but you were busy.
You were talking to that other lad.
Jacob?
Yeah, I just... I didn't want to interrupt.
Interrupt what?
Nothing's happening there.
Tonight or any other night
in the indefinite future.
[chuckles nervously]
Okay.
[Darren] Um...
[Cash] Oi. Let me make it up to you.
[squeals]
Little shits just did a cock-and-run.
Fucking twinks.
♪ In your mind
It's kind of what I'm like ♪
♪ Take your time
Baby, I'm just what you like ♪
[upbeat music playing]
♪ My Quinni the Pooh ♪
What's up?
I said that I was okay with you not coming
to Darren's party, but I wasn't.
We made plans and since then
my entire night has been out of whack.
I'm sorry. It's just, time got away
from me at Missy's
and I know routine is important for you...
Oh, my God. It is a shitty thing
for anyone to be stood up.
Okay.
I was so looking forward
to hanging out tonight
and I get here and I see
you in a toilet cubicle with Missy and...
- But I know you don't want to do drugs.
- How do you know?
Oh, so you do want to do drugs?
That's not the point.
I don't need you
to make that decision for me.
But understand that I don't want
to be responsible for you
if you have a bad reaction to anything.
You are not responsible for me. I am.
You're right.
It's just...
It's just that I care about you a lot.
A lot, a lot. A lot. I love you a lot.
- You're high.
- [chuckles]
Yeah.
- Yes, I am.
- Yes, you are.
But I mean it.
["BIG" playing]
I love you too.
Really?
♪ Watch were I step
'Cause I don't want no cracks ♪
♪ And I care way more
About my momma's back ♪
♪ I get anxious, over thinking... ♪
Did you see her arms?
She would've bashed us.
- Stupid.
- [both laughing]
♪ Cards to my chest with a poker face ♪
♪ See right through like I'm cellophane ♪
♪ I have trouble with commitment
Boy, come get... ♪
Can I kiss you?
Yes, please.
♪ Different walks of life
But in the end, we all bleed ♪
♪ Everybody working
'Cause we all gotta eat ♪
♪ Remind myself that it's bigger than me ♪
- ♪ Bigger than me ♪
- ♪ Bigger ♪
- ♪ Bigger than you and me ♪
♪ Bigger than ♪
- ♪ Bigger than me, ah, ah ♪
- ♪ Bigger ♪
- ♪ Bigger than me ♪
- ♪ Bigger than you and me ♪
- ♪ Bigger ♪
- ♪ Bigger than me ♪
["Sweat" playing]
♪ Physical regime
Making all the windows steam ♪
♪ Do you need to catch your breath? ♪
♪ Do it fast or do it slow
High impacted cardio ♪
♪ Think you might be out of your depth ♪
♪ What you wanna take tonight? ♪
[song continues in distance]
[indistinct chatter]
How good was that, bro?
Whoa, whoa. You feel that?
No.
That's boyfriend material.
Oh. [Chuckles]
So?
You really want an answer right now?
Why not?
Are you still angry with me?
No, I'm not wild with you.
Are you still into Dusty?
No.
I saw you looking at him earlier.
I wasn't.
Not Dusty...
Harper.
What?
I still don't know what happened,
but she broke my heart
and I don't know if I ever want
to feel hurt like that again.
[chuckles]
Well, I'm not Harper. I'm Malakai.
No, you're drunk.
A little bit cute, ey?
Little bit.
[cop] Time to go, guys!
Ooh. Malakai, the cop's coming.
Finish what you were going to say.
Malakai, we're leaving...
- You were about to tell me. Come on.
- Malakai.
- [Malakai chuckles]
- Let's go.
They won't do anything.
- You don't know that.
- Come on.
Party's over! It's time to move on!
Clear the streets.
The party poopers have come
to poop on our party. [Chuckles]
Time to go, champ.
Yeah, we're going.
- Get going.
- [Amerie] We're going, sir.
Good night, officer.
No crims on the street, ey? [Chuckles]
Move.
Hey, too rough.
Fuck off, dog.
[Malakai gasps]
[Amerie] Malakai!
[Dusty] Oi! What the fuck?!
[clubbers yelling, shouting]
[gasping]
[Amerie] What are you doing?!
Get out of here!
Get away from him!
[crowd clamoring]
[coughing]
[Amerie] Malakai!
Wait. Wait, Malakai. Are you okay?
That was so messed up.
I knew they would do something!
Why didn't you listen?
What are you yelling at me for?
They didn't come after you.
[panting] Did anyone...
Did any of you film it?
Did you get it?
Yeah. Here.
- Can you send it to me?
- Yeah.
[breathing heavily]
We gotta expose them.
We need to share this.
No, don't do that. Don't do that!
- But Malakai, what?
- No, don't.
The people need to know!
We need to let people know.
Nothing is going to happen.
Nothing ever happens to them.
I'll get shit for it.
[Spider] Shouldn't have sworn at him.
[all yell] Shut the fuck up, Spider!
Malakai, that was so, so wrong.
You need to let people know, tell someone.
Amerie, just leave it. No!
I said no! All right, just listen to me.
Okay.
- Okay. I'll...
- [cell phone chimes]
Shit. Um...
- What?
- I, um...
- I can... I'm just gonna delete it.
- Did you just post it?
[Amerie] I'm so sorry. I um...
What the fuck? I told you to leave... Fuck!
I'm sorry...
- Fuck off! Get away from me. Get away!
- I'll delete it now!
Just get out of my life!
- What? Are you...
- Fuck off!
I want to be alone!
Just leave me alone. I...
[Malakai crying]
Don't let him go.
Amerie.
Don't just let him walk away.
You heard him. It's done.
[uneasy music playing]
[Malakai crying]
- [Dusty] It's okay, man.
- It's okay.
Hey, it's okay.
You're safe now. It's okay.
[crying]
["Describe" playing on speakers]
♪ No bells anymore ♪
♪ Just my stomach rumbling ♪
[inaudible]
♪ Can you describe them for me? ♪
♪ The lock on the door ♪
♪ Is barely holding ♪
♪ Can you just wait here with me? ♪
♪ Ooh, his lovin' felt like ribbons ♪
♪ Ooh, an echo in the canyon ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm